<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Staff on </title>
    <link>https://curating4reproducibility.org/contributors/staff/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Staff on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 14:30:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://curating4reproducibility.org/contributors/staff/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Save the Date: CURE Workshop at IDCC 2018</title>
      <link>https://curating4reproducibility.org/news/save-the-date-cure-workshop-at-idcc-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 14:30:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://curating4reproducibility.org/news/save-the-date-cure-workshop-at-idcc-2018/</guid>
      <description>The CURE team will be hosting a half-day workshop at the 13th International Digital Curation Conference (IDCC) in Barcelona on February 19, 2018 from 9:30 to 12:30.
The workshop, &amp;ldquo;Curating for Reproducibility: Producing High Quality Data and Code for Transparent and Reproducible Research,&amp;rdquo; will teach participants practical strategies for curating research materials to support reproducible science.
The workshop will be based on the Data Quality Review, a framework for helping ensure that research data are well documented and usable, and that code executes properly and reproduces analytic results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CURE Receives IMLS Grant</title>
      <link>https://curating4reproducibility.org/news/cure-receives-imls-grant/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 16:12:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://curating4reproducibility.org/news/cure-receives-imls-grant/</guid>
      <description>We are excited to announce that CURE has been awarded a grant from the Institute of Museum and Library Services as part of the Laura Bush 21th Century Librarian Program. The grant will be used to support the development of an evidence-based training program for librarians and archivists focused on data curation for reproducibility. The training program is intended to equip its participants with the skills needed to ensure the quality of research data, the demand for which has never been higher.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
